목요일 밤은 'Ladies' Night' 이라고
Thursday night is Ladies' Night.
무슨 말이냐면, 오늘 밤이 깊어갈수록
Which means, as the evening progresses,
99센트짜리 마가리타와 반값의 젤로샷 덕분에 우리가 잘생겨 보일거란 뜻이지
we will get better looking courtesy of 99 cent margaritas and two-for-one Jell-O shots.
관둬, 하워드.. 우리가 술집에서 여자를 꼬실 확률은 사실상 제로야
Come on, Howard, the odds of us picking up girls in a bar are practically zero.
아, 그래? 드레이크 방정식이라고 들어는 봤냐?
Oh, really? Are you familiar with the Drake Equation?
행성을 거느린 항성의 비율과 생명이 탄생 가능한 행성의 개수같은
The one that estimates the odds of making contact with extraterrestrials
점점 더 제한적인 일련의 소수를 모두 곱해서
by calculating the product of an increasingly restrictive series of fractional values
우리가 외계인과 조우할 가능성을 구하는 공식이지
such as those stars with planets, and those planets likely to develop life?